FANSUB GROUP AZALIA PRESENTS
Worked on the series:
Lily, Tiramisu, Biryulka, Host, Hazelnut, February
How did I become
queen
All characters are fictitious
and the events shown are fiction.
If you don't want to talk,
do we use hand signals?
AZALEA
For example, this one.
What is this?
This means that I'm lying about everything.
What do you say? It's not difficult, is it?
The king never lies.
Episode 15
What sin could such a young child commit?
The smell of alcohol and something else.
She didn't drink poison.
I can't believe she was forced to drink poison with those tiny hands.
Hands are warm. She's still alive.
Get up.
Damhyang!
Your Majesty.
-Mr.
-You are here.
Mister.
Hold it.
You cannot leave your child in the mountains.
I have to give her a funeral.
-Goodbye.
How's Damhyang doing? Is she okay?
She had already left the palace safely.
I had mercy on her servant mother
and prepared everything so that they would leave Hanyang together.
So she will meet her mother.
Damhyang was very worried about her.
What a joy. This is cool.
How did you pull this off? Did you give her sleeping pills?
She was given mafeisan to drink.
Mafeisan, what did Hua Tuo use during operations?
You know him.
Certainly. I have read The Three Kingdoms for Children many times.
Three Kingdoms for children?
Listen to me. You should have warned me.
The matter was urgent
It was dangerous to involve many people.
Any news from Mr. Hong?
Yes. He made sure the child escaped safely.
Well done.
Recklessly putting yourself in danger
because of the maid.
She's not just a maid.
If I gave up my child,
it would be easier to give up 10, 100,
and then all my people.
I thought Cheoljong was an ordinary fool,
and he's just an incredible fool.
Don't spend a lot of time thinking about great things.
Otherwise you won't live long.
I don't intend to live a miserable life.
A perfect excuse for an early death.
Yes, because of whom is he...
This is how she thanks me.
The Queen speaks differently than others.
The Queen's Dictionary came in handy.
It is full of loose and incorrect translations.
-Have you seen him?
-You left it open.
By the way, is the queen's position always this dangerous?
Why does everyone want to kill me?
I won't let this happen again.
No. I'll take care of everything myself.
The best defense is attack.
From this day on, I will become the most reckless one in the palace.
Crazy X is here
Have you tried to get rid of the queen?
The queen is on the king's side.
She told him about all the weaknesses of our family.
She fell in love with the king and turned away from us.
This is not true.
You don't want to believe
that the queen you adore
just a stupid woman
recklessly in love with a man.
Having joined your family,
I did everything you wanted to be accepted.
Not just to stay in this house.
I wanted to be like you
had respect for you.
But trying to harm the queen
you are no longer my father.
If anyone decides to threaten the queen,
I will definitely cut his throat.
You can come home whenever you want.
Even if you don't consider me a father,
you will always be my son.
Who could have hidden the ledger in Daejojeon?
The main suspects are
those two who harbored a grudge against me.
The Queen Mother and Cho Hwajin.
The motive points to Cho Hwajin.
I'm almost sure, considering
how she behaved during the hunt.
However, Hwajin had not come to Daejojong for a long time.
Methods point to the Queen Mother.
Here.
She comes here suspiciously often lately.
Of course, she also has a motive.
Is this the Queen Mother?
This little rat.
How did the Queen Mother get her hands on the ledger?
That's the mystery.
And more importantly, what kind of ledger is this?
I didn't perform the ritual today.
I apologize for my rude behavior.
You're apologizing for a reason.
What is the reason?
As I expected
you grasp everything on the fly.
Thank you for participating in this unpleasant meeting.
I'm sure in light of recent events you understand
that the time has come to know
unite families.
We are closely connected.
If one of the two families falls,
the other will not stay afloat.
Therefore, I propose to issue a decree on amnesty,
as a guarantee of harmony in relationships.
Decree?
Many talents from both families
lost their posts due to a momentary mistake.
We will issue an amnesty decree to pardon these people.
In other words, it is a symbol of promise
and a congratulatory gift.
What do you say?
Can you support me on this?
The War Department used dirty tricks to satisfy their greed,
and I am guilty of not being able to subdue him.
In this regard, I, Kim Jwageun,
I ask for resignation from my post.
It's not over yet for me.
It won't end as long as I breathe.
Eat more slowly.
Are there enough snacks?
I shouldn't eat if I have even an ounce of shame left in me.
So why did you run away?
I treated you well.
The thing is...
Mom.
Mother.
God.
You've suffered enough, Damhyang.
It was hard for you.
Everything is fine.
Everything will be fine.
We try to smile in front of her.
Her Majesty should not
grieve for a long time.
Yes.
Your Majesty. It's time to wake up.
Your Majesty.
Were you unable to sleep last night?
I'm worried you'll get yourself into trouble.
Too many thoughts, I couldn’t sleep.
By the way, did they sleep well anyway?
Who?
Those people who tried to ruin my life.
This was their last peaceful sleep.
I hope they got enough sleep.
-Lady Choi.
-Yes.
Send someone
for my father, let him come to the palace.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Your father has arrived.
Already?
I was going to ask you to come to the palace.
But you have already arrived.
Yes.
It seems that I came for a reason.
-Last time...
You speak first.
No. You speak.
No. You speak first.
-Sorry about that time.
-No. First I'll apologize.
-No. Me first.
-Me first.
-No, I.
-God.
-Me first.
Yes, blood is not water.
Exactly.
I called you today
because of the ledger.
-Did you know?
-Everyone went crazy because of her.
What kind of book is this?
This is an account of the illegal activities of our clan.
The weak point of the Andong Kim clan.
That's why Cheoljong wanted to get her.
Today I just came to talk about her.
After your visit with the king, she disappeared.
Therefore, all this time I suspected the king.
But recently
my faithful servant, whom I doted on, ran away.
Luckily, I caught it and found out the reason.
The day before the disappearance
he let concubine Cho in.
When there was a commotion at home,
he thought it was all because of him and ran away. Therefore...
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
Here
and our riddle was solved.
What?
Sunwon was the one who initiated my murder.
I specially prepared ice
which is more expensive than gold today.
The Queen Mother mocked me.
I will serve you my food someday.
I have to try it now.
And Cho Hwajin provided the weapon.
Confess everything to the king.
Are you threatening me?
I you
heard clearly.
Father, I need to go somewhere now.
Where?
Open the door to the fire pit.
You will regret contacting me.
She used to be as obedient as a lamb.
And in a short time here she became cruel.
I know that parents cannot be objective towards their children.
But a sheep?
If I compared her to an animal,
then only with tarpan.
My daughter is a Tarpan?
Maori tattoo.
Peacock feather.
And the devil wears Prada.
There is power in beauty.
Today I have the most beautiful armor.
How do you like it?
Like.
Revenge is sweet when served with fireworks.
What does it mean?
What you see is not everything.
To find out what's inside,
needs to be cut.
I thought it was just potatoes.
But you fooled me.
You should not lose trust without a good reason.
You need to make sure what it is before you cut it.
Because after that you won’t get anything back.
Your drinks.
Today I prepared brunch
to thank you for the recent
wonderful breakfast.
The cool drink at last brunch was so great
that I wouldn't even notice someone's death.
Give it a try.
I don't feel like drinking.
I put so much effort into it. Take at least a sip.
I said that I don’t want to.
I tried so hard.
If you don't want to drink...
It really tastes better with ice.
I said before that I will help you
stay healthy and young for the rest of your life.
And I will continue to do so.
If you doubt food, drinks and everything around you,
then life will turn into nothing but suffering.
Since my regency is over,
Do you think you can do anything?
Do you think you'll stay
a queen without her clan?
The Dowager Queen.
I don't rely on my clan or my husband.
I do whatever I want because I can.
Exactly. Chief Eunuch.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I neglected my duty
produce an heir.
I think this is unacceptable.
So go and report to her.
Report?
I don't know what you're talking about, Your Majesty.
You know, you always do this.
How dare you?
I should punish you!
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
-Kill me.
-What's wrong with you?
I didn't tell you.
Now my life is in your hands.
I don't need her.
What should I do with it?
Please kill me, Your Majesty.
God. I said it's not necessary.
I know you had no choice.
You must follow orders.
It would be better if you were angry with me.
It's scarier.
How can you be a spy if you're so easily scared?
I need to go somewhere before the meeting.
Go to Injeongjeong.
God, can you read this somewhere else?
The chief eunuch was so scared.
Hope you slept well.
Is this how you greet your elders?
The stilettos are very heavy.
I can't bow my head.
In this sacred place, rituals are performed and ancestors are remembered.
It's not appropriate to come here hung with jewelry.
Before you issue a return, you need to clean the feathers.
Wow, I completely forgot.
We need to light incense for the deceased king.
And how could I disgrace the Chonghak teaching on etiquette.
Stop it.
I am an ardent follower of Confucianism.
I can't stand unfulfilled rituals.
I told you not to touch it.
You left something in my chambers.
They showed up unannounced and poked their nose into my affairs.
About the same as now.
What are you doing?
She said so. Return.
I suffered a lot here - I need to return everything.
What kind of rude words are you talking?
Slander your elders
and complain about life.
You've always been like this
but today your temper has crossed all boundaries.
Is it because you grew up without your mother's hand?
Hey, mother-in-law.
If I'm rude because I grew up without a mother,
then you are impudent because you did not raise your child?
Hot!
Everything is so annoying that I can't stand the heat.
Portrait of your dearest son
Almost got burned.
Are you out of your mind?
Yes, for sure and irrevocably.
Of all the crazy people, I'm the maddest.
So go ahead and look around.
Even if a hair falls from my head,
and you won’t see your son again.
It wasn't the queen that was worth worrying about,
and about all the others.
The best defense is an attack.
Wow, I didn’t notice that you were here too.
There are ghost people.
They walk and do not show any light.
I'm throwing pancakes into the pond here.
Do you want to come with me?
Throw it yourself.
Accounting book.
You're the one who took it.
I almost died because of her.
Tell me.
Did you achieve this?
You really didn't kill Ovol?
No matter what I say, you only believe what you want.
I must take the king from you,
kill Ovol and throw her body into the well.
Then I'll be a villain who deserves to die
and you are an innocent victim, saint.
This is why playing the victim is dangerous.
Slowly turning into a monster -
and you yourself don’t notice.
Look in the mirror.
You will see your ugliness.
Stay on your own if you want to get out.
There is no mood for good deeds.
When I fell into the water before your eyes,
most likely
you could have extended your hand to me.
This proves
that as a person I am better than you.
Kim Jwageun, troop commander,
left his post.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The resignation was delayed
you could all repent for this.
What a shame.
Wait, I misspoke.
What a relief.
Next question.
But first I want to announce something.
I will create an agency that will deal with the system of three taxes.
It will be called Samjeong Lijeongjeong.
Samjeong Lijeongjeon?
It will create laws
and develop plans to solve
the main shortcomings of the three-tax system.
The country lives off agriculture.
The peasants prosper, and she prospers.
Officials robbing ordinary farmers
- a threat to the state.
Their atrocities will be regarded as treason.
Before creating a new agency
you need to study everything carefully.
At least listen to our opinion before...
I won't make any concessions
doing what you have to do.
This means
that your opinion no longer matters.
I will also give the late King Seongjong
posthumous name Sunjo, as required by tradition.
His Majesty is more assertive than usual today.
Your Majesty.
Today there is a new appointment.
The chief secretary misspoke.
We are talking about a candidate proposal.
The position of the Minister of War is vacant.
A weak army will lead to a crisis throughout the country.
So I insist that you approve
candidate chosen by the military council.
The Minister of War is coming.
Kim Byongin, Minister of War
Greetings Your Majesty.
Kim Byungin may be dangerous - he is supported by the Cho family.
Both Cho and Kim
asked for him.
This must be his doing too.
I don't think we can turn a blind eye to their requests.
This could give the aristocrats a reason to rebel.
Now you are free to do
whatever you want.
But it is still difficult to stop their attacks.
The best defense is an attack.
Need to strike
faster than your opponent.
There is no time to recruit more soldiers.
I want you to take care of Lijonchon.
Hon, I'll send you
to 3 cities in the south.
People there are indignant - start an investigation.
Another business trip?
Well, for my sake.
The further into the forest, the more you are here
the two of you sit and give orders.
It seems like all the running is on me. Or am I wrong?
Not just on you. I always...
When you're done with your investigation,
-I could give you a vacation.
-I'm leaving.
I could.
I said I could.
I doubt he heard it.
What an idiot.
Your Majesty.
There is a letter for you.
I won't kill you, come closer.
The Queen has sent you a letter.
Are you sick?
You shake like an autumn leaf.
Revenge was not what I thought.
It should have been more fun.
How exciting.
I'm shaking all over.
His Majesty...
You have come.
Today you are especially beautiful.
It suits you very well.
Anything suits a pretty face.
I’ll be a beauty even in rags.
Who knew that I would become a great queen?
I'll never get used to this.
I asked for a meeting
to propose an alliance.
Rod probably left me
thinking that now I'm at one with you.
I have nothing to lose.
If you choose my side
The Kim family will become your enemy.
They were the first to ditch me.
Now I'll throw them.
A common enemy is not a reason to unite?
Yes.
From now on, no social distancing.
Certainly. You can touch everything.
In films about bandits
I saw the homies mixing blood in a bowl and drinking.
But blood is somehow unhygienic.
Let's celebrate our union with tea.
Simple and tasteful.
What?
Is this how the allies drink?
Yes, for brotherhood.
-To the bottom.
-What...
Since we're brothers, let's clear things up.
Why did you want to kill me?
Right.
It's worth discussing.
We thought you heard our conversation
about the assassination attempt on your father.
He's still your father-in-law.
For me, he was one of the corrupt officials.
Heartless.
Everything is clear with you.
And he didn’t spare his own wife.
Serial killer Kimov.
Sorry.
I know my apologies won't change much
but there was so much misunderstanding between us.
OK.
You'll owe me.
I won't forgive you until you return the favor.
So what do you want?
Strengthen your power?
This is just a way to restore our destroyed country.
I don’t think that the foundations of society can be easily changed.
Honestly, I like the method more than the goal.
If you strengthen your power,
then no one will get to me.
I am well aware of the fear of death.
I know you're being rude
but you must be scared.
Don't know.
Maybe because she was already dying?
For me, neglect is worse than death.
If I can give a thrashing to all those who disdain me,
then I'll die smiling.
Your Majesty.
It's time to cook lunch.
Yes. Well then
I'm leaving you.
I'll die smiling.
"I'll die smiling."
- Mister Kim.
-Benin.
That is, the Minister of War.
-Are you kidding me?
-Why, of course not.
Please call me by name.
Actually, I was waiting for you
because I wanted to talk to you about the queen.
By the way, I also have something to tell you about her.
Where did I put this?
Where to?
-Wait.
-I saw.
You!
How dare you use a knife?
You've been here for almost a week.
Now everything has changed.
Lately, chefs have been refusing to drink makgeolli after work.
They constantly say “no” and “no”.
I said that I would treat them, but they still refuse.
Go and understand them.
I don’t understand these court ladies either.
I told them to come later, and they really came later.
They should have arrived early.
-Well, what kind of children have we gone?
To the Dongmyeongjong Hall.
Damn it.
There's one more thing left to take revenge on.
A recipe for revenge?
I can answer him the same, right?
An eye for an eye. A tooth for a tooth.
Manhood for manhood.
Fern then?
-Busennik?
-Fern and beaded plant.
This recipe has a lot of healthy ingredients.
So I will forever go towards my goal.
This is too long.
Let's go all in.
-Castration.
-Castration?
I didn't hear...
I see.
Such a valuable ingredient.
I don't want to burden you.
I know when to give up.
Sorry.
Don't apologize.
Can I ask you just one question?
-Yes.
-Why do you
Don't like purposeful men?
I saw a lot of purposeful people in the palace
and how hard it was for them.
I'm afraid
and I don’t want this for myself.
Thanks for your answer.
Everything I would dare to want from you,
so that you always
smiled.
Oh, it's you.
Apparently this is the end.
You really have a sharp eye.
You understood everything right away.
How could I not understand when you cry like that?
Don't look.
I don't want to be seen like this.
Then go around the corner and cry there.
People will still decide that it's because of me.
It's not because of me.
I won't cry anymore.
Being able to completely get rid of feelings is part of love.
This may be more difficult than continuing to love her.
You are truly a poet.
Let's go. Don't cry.
Did she send me food on purpose?
What is this ominous drawing?
How beautiful it is.
Court lady Chon, even poison would not take you,
You're so slow on the uptake.
Why are you suddenly praising me?
Your Majesty.
I, Simon of the Khan family, have come to greet you.
Haven't we met before?
I'm so grateful.
I mean, I... Please forgive me.
I think you should tell me something else.
For example,
"I deserve to die."
Because of you, I spilled all the popcorn I worked so hard to make.
Scattered when you sent it flying.
I had no idea that there was a queen in front of me,
I committed a serious crime.
Had no idea it was me?
Then why did you run away?
Well, that's because...
Such a noble man ran after me,
So I was surprised.
I had no other reasons.
Is it true?
In truth, I called you
to give you a place at court.
A good place where you definitely won’t be kicked out
and they will pay well.
But you have to lose something.
What?
Are you saying that I will lose something?
When I met you, even if it was short-lived,
I realized that this position is for you.
I'm so grateful to you, queen.
you
you will become a eunuch.
What?
Wait. Just a second.
Let me go. Hands off.
Your Majesty.
Please have mercy.
Thank you for your boundless generosity.
But why are you doing this?
Firstly,
you forged your identity as a nobleman.
No. It's not your fault.
The social structure is to blame for this.
Right.
At first. Firstly,
poisoned the water in the royal kitchen
and disrupted the royal feast.
Secondly,
your descendant is a terrible person.
Descendant?
Are you sure you haven't confused him with my ancestor?
No.
That's right.
Your descendant is a terrible person.
Descendant?
Your Majesty.
If I become a eunuch, there will be no descendants.
If I become a eunuch, there will be no descendants. Your Majesty!
I will have no descendants.
Do you have descendants? No?
I won't have any descendants!
How so. Queen!
Your Majesty, the Minister of War has arrived.
Your Majesty.
Andon clan Kim.
I'm sure they're all in cahoots.
But my dad is also from the Andong family of Kim.
What? I just called him “my dad.”
Transference of emotions is dangerous.
I found out what happened to you after our meeting.
I didn't know what happened.
You didn't know
that they were trying to kill me?
I am not on my father's side, and I am not part of the Kim family.
However, you are not free from your father and family.
Eventually you will understand.
Enemy or ally?
How dare he do this to Soyeon?
Moreover, how could he do this to the queen?
Kim Jwageun, you bastard.
I have to...
Besides, this Samjeong Lijeongjeong.
They use official corruption as an excuse
to try to destroy our family.
Don't worry.
If they see this as appropriation of someone else's property,
then no one is innocent.
To protect yourself
they will try to protect officials too.
All that will remain of the Samjeong Lijeongjeong is its outer shell.
Even if you join them for a while,
Keep your eyes on the Queen Mother.
She can smile in your face
but she is always ready to stab her in the back.
I will remember this.
Court lady Chon.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Clear the table and call the doctor.
Have you eaten yet?
I have no appetite.
I heard you liked the food
cooked by the queen.
She wasn't that good.
It was edible.
The Queen is grieving now.
She said that the main concubine
came between you and made her believe that the family had turned against her.
She blames herself for everything.
Main concubine?
The queen's father told me today.
It was not the queen who deceived you,
and the main concubine.
The king has granted.
Ask him to come in.
Your Majesty.
Sorry for the late visit without warning.
Everything is fine.
It's a huge honor any time.
I came to say something.
So what?
Regarding the body of a court maid recently found in a well.
This was done by order of the Queen Mother.
Queen Mothers?
But why would she...
You also can’t understand the reason?
If so, that's for sure...
It can't be Ovol.
But this is impossible. This is definitely Ovol.
I heard it was in such a state
which is difficult to identify.
Why did you decide that it was Ovol?
She was dressed as a court lady,
and of the court ladies, only Ovol disappeared.
She knew that you would think it was Ovol.
The Queen Mother wants
for you to rely on her.
But why was the well used?
I told her what I went through in the well.
That I met you in it.
And that this place hurts me.
He reminded me of you
so I was sure that I had lost someone dear to me.
Now I understand that you can’t carelessly reveal your pain.
to anyone in the palace.
Plunge the queen into the nightmare I live in.
Trust the Queen Mother no more.
We must hide what we all know
so don’t let her know that you know what she did.
She betrayed me and I am deeply disappointed.
Well for me
source of fear.
I can't believe she used that.
It's similar to poker and hato.
Chatting and games -
the best way to pass the time and life.
Glad to hear that.
We were afraid that Damhyang would make you feel bad.
Oh, sorry.
Don't worry. She's in a good place now.
Is it true? She had to go to a good place, right?
Damhyang.
No, that's not what I mean. She's really in a good place.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Damhyang.
She said she really moved to a good place.
Why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
If you think about it
I didn’t even say goodbye to her.
Damhyang.
-Damhyang.
-Queen.
Damhyang.
Seven.
Eight.
This is...
nine.
Forgive me.
How so?
-Damhyang.
All-in.
How did the Queen Mother get her hands on the ledger?
The book we searched so hard for but missed.
Maybe he could win her over to your side?
Joke.
Hearing that she had galloped ahead of us, who were freely leaving the palace,
I was disappointed in myself.
The Queen Mother is almost
all the time in the Seongwonjong Hall.
I don't understand how she got her hands on the ledger.
This and that she did with the body,
means she has accomplices.
Maybe we can make them our accomplices?
Is the portrait of the one in the tokkaebi mask not ready yet?
I've been too busy these days
freeing Damhyang's mother from slavery
and looking for her father.
But you never found him, did you?
How to find someone hiding in the mountains?
He probably became a bandit.
Thinking about a holiday after a trip as a royal investigator,
I can barely stand these days.
Actually, what I meant was...
Can you make me a secret inspector instead of a royal investigator?
This is cooler.
Having disguised myself, I would suddenly take out a token, like this!
Yes, you are a born secret inspector. Do as you please.
One more time.
I don't think Youngjin is that kind of person.
Only Kim Jwageun deserved to die.
And Youngjin -
my whole family.
Hey, you'll sleep here after that
how he almost killed his father-in-law and wife?
Apparently not.
Heart, stop it.
It hurts my pride.
Looks like she's been underwater for a long time.
I understand how painful it must be.
The fact that her body was found in a well is either a terrible coincidence,
or someone wants to push us.
I thought deeply.
You must be very shocked.
There's too much space here for me.
Here you feel lonely and lost.
I found the maid who sold the noriga that you gave Ovol.
She said she found it in the palace.
Is that so?
This is the same maid who threw the body into the well
by order of the Queen Mother.
Ovol is alive.
She was attacked in the palace.
She didn’t even have time to take a step outside the palace.
Didn't you hope that the body
What was found in the well did not belong to Ovol?
Shouldn't you be happy?
that it was not Ovol?
Why do you believe that this is Ovol?
For God's sake...
For God's sake, what are you hiding?
Last time
what did you convey
Queen Mother?
Have you seen everything?
I
I don't see anything without your permission.
Everyone goes astray at times.
You still have a chance to get back on the right track.
What if I've lost my way a long time ago?
I still can
back on track?
There is no turning back.
Your Highness.
That body must be Ovol.
Why do you make Samhyang Ramen?
in the middle of the night?
Why do you want it most at night?
You know that your face will be swollen in the morning.
But it is so difficult to fight temptation.
You tried so hard, it's a shame it was in vain.
Queen Dowager at night
doesn't eat.
So instead let me...
No.
You must warn me when you are coming.
Why didn't you even knock?
Do you want us to eat some ramen before we leave?
What is ramen? And where do you want me to go?
No pressure. This is just research.
Or a test.
No, I shouldn't do that.
But if only a little...
No, no.
Ramen has such an addictive taste.
Once you start, it’s impossible to stop.
What are you doing?
Internal conflict.
What would you do if you were me?
Would you eat ramen or not?
I think I would first explain what ramen is.
-For starters...
-What?
I'll try it.
Is it true?
You will only understand what it is when you try it.
It's like air when you get drunk
or when you're angry,
or realize what it is
reality.
Are we speaking the same language now?
Certainly.
We're talking about ramen.
Move closer. Ramen is good when it's hot.
Initial Instruction for Children
How do you treat her?
Oh, mommies!
What to do? This is a priceless book.
Why did you say this book is priceless?
Why is Primary Instruction for Children valuable to you?
This is...
Was it you?
The one who saved me was you?
Did you save me from the well?
Yes.
It was me.
How I became queen
My Cheoljong will be desperately waiting for me.
So is this a trap?
I can't believe the queen challenged me to a real fight.
-Now is it my turn?
-Take out your sword.
The one who doesn’t clean up after himself and leaves traces,
must answer for everything.
Even though I overthrew the Kim clan,
Kim Byonin's power only grew stronger.
It feels like there is no progress.
If Cheoljong does this, the world will also change 200 years later.
As long as I'm on your side, you will win.
I have a secret weapon.
I know the future.